RG 062:125, Town of Sharon
Connecticut State Library
Town of Sharon records
1760-1976
Connecticut State Library
Sharon (Conn.)
39 cubic feet
Administrative, poor relief, land, court, military, vital, school, church, election, tax, and committee records for the town of Sharon.
RG062_125
2008-007
Historical Note
The town of Sharon was incorporated in October 1739. It is located in Litchfield County.
Scope and Content
Series 1. Administrative Records, 1760-1938, 1971, contain a variety of papers including bonds, corporation reports, appointment of overseers, roads and highways, appointment of overseers, petitions, selectmen's report, town meeting notices and votes and treasurer's records. Nineteenth century town officials were generally bonded and the records contain bonds primarily for collector and constable although bonds for town clerk and treasurer are also present. There are also bonds for the keeping of a victualling house and for the sale of liquor. Corporations represented in the corporation reports are the Amenia and Sharon Land Company, Sharon Valley Malleable and Gray Iron Company, Sharon Valley Iron Company and Webotuck Mining Company. Appointments of overseers were made by selectmen over those who were not capable of handling their own affairs. Petitions to the selectmen ask for special town meetings to be called. Reasons include a proposed addition to the town hall, selling of liquor, taxes, auditing of town treasurer and collector, and the alteration of a highway from Cornwall Bridge to Ellsworth. Town governments devoted considerable time and attention to the construction and maintenance of roads and highways. The bulk of the papers related to this activity are surveys but costs, assessments of damages, a description of highway districts, and receipts for maintenance are also present. Annual financial reports of the selectmen contain the type of information that is later printed in town reports. The bulk of the town meeting notices and votes concern the annual election of officers and adopting of town resolutions. Among the treasurer's records are four volumes of journals, two volumes of town orders, as well as correspondence, orders received from justices of the peace, notes for money owed the town, receipts for payments made, and annual reports. Also present is an 1829 copy of the patent for Sharon and a 1879 copy of the resolution incorporating the town.
Series 2. Poor Relief Records, 1804-1865, contain bonds, contracts, indentures, selectmen's accounts with town poor, and town farm records. Bonds include some given by men for the support of children they fathered. Contracts are between the selectmen and either individuals hired to manage the town farm or physicians for providing care to the paupers at the town farm. Indentures are contracts, usually between the selectmen and masters, that bind poor children who are either orphans or whose parents cannot provide for them into service until the age of twenty-one. The contracts provide a list of prohibitions imposed on the children together with the obligation of masters to provide clothing, education, and training for the apprentices. The selectmen's accounts with town poor record expenses associated with care of the poor. Town farm records include account books and annual reports. Two of the account books were kept by Thomas N. Lukas between 1840 and 1843.
Series 3. Land Records, 1807-1921, contain agreements, deeds, foreclosures, leases and notices of lis pendens, and miscellaneous papers.
Series 4. Court Records, 1788-1946, contain primarily justice files, 1818-1908. Much of this is writs or summonses that name the plaintiff and defendant, describe the offense, specify the date the two parties are to appear, and the name of the justice of the peace trying the case. Other types of documents are certificates of attachment and criminal complaints. While most of the cases involve the settlement of debt, cases of assault, theft, illegal sale of liquor, and intoxication are also present. A number of different Justices are represented. There is also a justice book kept by David Downs between 1788 and 1791. Two volumes of attachments cover 1859 to 1946. There is also a small volume of juror lists, justice of the peace lists, Probate Court material, and miscellaneous papers. To the west of Sharon is the town of Amenia, New York. Consequently, there is a small volume of papers from Dutchess County Supreme Court.
Series 5. Military Records, 1812-1951, contain papers relating to the Civil War, World War I, and World War II. Included are also three volumes of enrollment books covering 1853 to 1922.
Series 6. Vital Records, 1828-1892, contain information on births, marriages and deaths.
Series 7. School Records, 1796-1911, contain district returns, minute books for some districts, reports and records related to the town deposit fund.
Series 8. Church Records, 1855-1884, consists only of two types of documents related to the Methodist Episcopal Church, those dealing with the election of trustees and a subscription list.
Series 9. Election Records, 1855-1967, contain a variety of records including admission of electors and certifications of electors, election notices, election returns, and voting lists. Certification of electors represents documentation between town clerks of different towns attesting that a person who has moved to a new town was a legal voter in his former town of residence. Election returns cover State officers including Governor, Lieutenant Governor, Secretary, Treasurer and Comptroller; Federal offices such as Electors of President and Vice President, Senator, and Representative in Congress; State offices such as Senator and Representative in the General Assembly; and local offices such as sheriff and Judge of Probate. Voting lists are of two types: certified lists, in which the Registrars certify the number of electors and votes cast, and check lists.
Series 10. Tax Records, 1812-1939, contains abatements, assessment books, list books, individual tax lists, and tax abstracts. The tax abstracts have separate columns for name, number of polls, military commutation tax, and various types of property such as houses, land, horses, cattle, money at interest, and luxury goods such as coaches, watches, and musical instruments. Automobiles appeared in 1910.
Series 11. Committee Records, 1939, 1976, contain material from the town Bicentennial Committee. The town of Sharon celebrated its bicentennial in 1939. There is also a few items of ephemera from to the U.S. Bicentennial.
Related Material
Proprietors records, 1758-1822, 2 volumes. Photostat copies of 3rd and 4th books. [CSL call number StLib Archives 974.62 Sh2p].
School records, enumeration returns, 1847-1856 [CSL call number StLib Archives 972.62 Sh 242]. Available on microfilm LH 4431.
School records of the Ellsworth school society. Includes school register for district No. 1, 1839-1843; account book of receipts and disbursements, 1815-1848; statements issued by Comptroller's office for dividends on school fund, 1815-1856; orders, 1802-1858; receipts, 1802-1851; teachers' certificates, 1818-1849; certificates issued by school visitors, 1818-1852; notices of meetings, 1843-1864; and miscellaneous [CSL call number StLib Archives 974.62 Sh242r]. Available on microfilm LH 4431.
Index Terms
Alternate author:
Connecticut. Justice of the peace (Sharon)
Subjects:
Taxation -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Registers; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Registers; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Sharon; Writs -- Connecticut -- Sharon; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Sharon; Voting -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Statistics; Elections -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Statistics; Soldiers -- Connecticut -- Sharon; Public welfare -- Connecticut -- Sharon; Deeds -- Connecticut -- Sharon; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Statistics; Schools -- Connecticut -- Sharon -- Records and correspondence
Places:
Sharon (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; Sharon (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital
Places:
Sharon (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
Box 13 is restricted due to condition. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
Boxes 21-28 are restricted. They may contain confidential personal data restricted by law. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Administrative Records, 1760-1938, 1971
  - Appointments and oaths of office, 1861, 1874-1896, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bonds (Box 1)
    - Collector, 1825-1887 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Constable, 1854-1898 (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
    - Town Clerk and Treasurer, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Victualling house and liquor, 1845-1862 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bridges, 1822-1823, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bridges: Public hearing transcript, Restoration of the covered bridge over the Housatonic River on Route 128, 1971 October 13 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Corporation reports (Box 1)
    - Amenia and Sharon Land Company, 1878-1883 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Sharon Valley Malleable and Gray Iron Company, 1876-1883 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1876-1883 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Includes papers for the Sharon Valley Iron Company and the Webotuck Mining Company.
  - Correspondence, 1820-1901 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dog registers
    - 1931-1936, 1 volume + 1 folder (Box 14)
      Folder contains loose items removed from volume.
    - 1941-1946, 1 volume + 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Ear marks, 1760-1845 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Insurance policies, 1837, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Liquor licenses, 1822-1828, 1866-1888, undated (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - Overseers, Appointments of, 1826-1886, bulk 1826-1842 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Papers, 1874, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Patent for and resolution incorporating Sharon, Copies of, 1829, 1878 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Petitions, 1882-1887, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Roads and highways (Box 1)
    - Costs, 1805-1820, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Damages, 1785-1804, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Highway districts, 1825 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Papers, 1803-1809, 1888, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Receipts, 1883-1885 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Surveys, 1784-1880, undated (Box 1, Folder 28-31)
  - Selectmen reports, 1827-1875 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
  - Town meetings (Box 2)
    - Notices for, 1809-1850-1851, 1862-1866, 1882-1891 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
    - Votes, 1793-1892, undated (Box 2, Folder 7-11)
  - Treasurer (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Bounties paid for wild cats, 1854-1856 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1862-1885 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Journals
      - 1868-1897, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1897-1906, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1914-1924, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1924-1938, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Justice orders, 1846-1868, 1881, undated (Box 2, Folder 14-17)
    - Notes, 1799-1857 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
    - Receipts, 1790-1820, 1846-1894, undated (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
    - Reports, 1810, 1855-1882, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - State tax and military commutation tax receipts, 1846-1885 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Tax collector receipts, 1845-1846 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Town order books
      - 1801-1816, 1 volume (Box 10)
      - 1816-1835, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Town orders, 1806, 1839-1890, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Fragments (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Series 2. Poor Relief Records, 1804-1865
  - Bonds, 1804-1865 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Contracts, 1829-1845 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Indentures, 1825-1843 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Julia Ann Reed, Papers relating to, 1836-1855 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Selectmen's accounts with town poor, 1792-1796 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Restricted due to condition. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
  - Town farm account books, 1840-1843, 1857-1858 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - Town farm reports, 1846-1865, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Series 3. Land Records, 1807-1921
  - Agreements, 1823, 1873-1890 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Deeds, 1807-1889 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Foreclosures, 1876-1882, 1901, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Index, undated (Box 14)
  - Leases, 1877-1880 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lis pendens, Notices of, 1903, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Papers, 1840-1908, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series 4. Court Records, 1788-1946
  - Attachments
    See also Series 5. Military Records. A volume of enrollments also contains Attachments, 1854-1859.
    - Number 1, 1859-1906; 1 volume (Box 11)
    - Number 2, 1907-1946; 1 volume (Box 11)
  - Dutchess County, N.Y. papers, 1862-1875, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dutchess County, N.Y. Supreme Court, 1869, 1875-1876 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
  - Jurors, 1883-1896 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Justice book, 1788-1791 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Justice files
    - 1818-1871 (Box 4, Folder 1-13)
    - 1872-1881, 1901-1908, undated (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
  - Justice of the Peace lists, 1854, 1874 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Papers, 1867, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Probate Court, 1848-1921, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Probate Court: Platt Smith estate, 1861-1863 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Series 5. Military Records, 1812-1951
  - Children of deceased soldiers, Payments to, 1866-1884 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Enrollment books
    - 1853-1870, 1 volume (Box 12)
      Also includes: List of voters, 1853; Book in reverse: Attachments, 1854-1859.
    - 1881-1913, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1913-1922, 1 volume (Box 12)
  - Enrollment of soldiers, circa 1861-1865 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Families of volunteers, Payments to, 1864-1865 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Papers, 1812-1887 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Registration for World War I (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1921 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Lists of men, circa 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Proclamation and circular letters, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Registrar's oaths, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Registration Board reports, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Registration cards, How to answer questions on, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Regulations, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Selective Service (Box 5)
  - Selective Service (Box 5)
    - Certificates of registrars and report of Registration Board, 1940, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1940, 1948-1951, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Men inducted, 1941-1944, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Papers, 1940, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Registration card receipts, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Veterans lists, 1948, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Series 6. Vital Records, 1828-1892
  - Abstracts of births, marriages and deaths, 1866 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Birth certificates, 1828, 1861, 1877-1879 (Box 5, Folder 28-30)
  - Death certificates, 1861, 1876-1882 (Box 5, Folder 31-32)
  - Italian subjects, Circular letter regarding, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Marriage consents, 1883, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Marriage intentions and licenses, 1860-1862, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
- Series 7. School Records, 1796-1968
  - District boundaries, 1799, 1820, 1845-1846, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - District returns, 1850-1851, 1859 (Box 6, Folder 2-4)
  - First School Society meeting notices, 1836-1850 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Minute books (Box 6)
    - School Society, 1796-1820 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - First School Society, 1821-1856 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Also includes Visitors' reports, 1846-1847 and school district boundaries, 1873.
    - District No. 1, 1855-1909 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - District No. 2, 1905-1909 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - District No. 3, 1816-1879 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - District no. 3, 1880-1909 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - District No. 5, 1800-1836, 1864-1866, 1873 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - District No. 13, 1891-1909 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - District No. 3 (Ellsworth Society), 15, 14, 1847-1909 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - School Visitors and School Committee, 1906-1910 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - School Committee, 1910-1911 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Reports on the condition of public schools, 1897-1898 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - School registers, 1894-1968
    Boxes 21-28 are restricted. They may contain confidential personal data restricted by law. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - 1894-1985, 1895, 1895-1896, 1896-1897, 1897-1898, 1898-1899, 1899, 1 folder (9 items) (Box 21)
      There are two items for 1895 and two for 1895-1896.
    - 1889-1896, 1 volume (Box 21)
    - 1896-1899, 1 volume (Box 21)
    - 1899-1905, 1 volume (Box 21)
    - 1905-1909, 1 volume (Box 21)
    - 1912-1915, 1 volume (Box 22)
    - 1916-1918, 1 volume (Box 22)
    - 1918-1921, 1 volume (Box 22)
    - 1921-1924, 1 volume (Box 22)
    - 1924-1927, 1 volume (Box 23)
    - 1927-1930, 1 volume (Box 23)
    - 1930-1932, 1 volume (Box 23)
    - 1937-1938, 1 volume (Box 23)
    - 1938-1939, 1 volume (Box 24)
    - 1943-1944, 1 volume (Box 24)
    - 1944-1945, 1 volume (Box 24)
    - 1946-1947, 1 volume (Box 24)
    - 1947-1948, 1 volume (Box 25)
    - 1948-1949, 1 volume (Box 25)
    - 1949-1950, 1 volume (Box 25)
    - 1950-1951, 1 volume (Box 25)
    - 1951-1952, 1 volume (Box 26)
    - 1952-1953, 1 volume (Box 26)
    - 1953-1954, 1 volume (Box 26)
    - 1954-1955, 1 volume (Box 26)
    - 1955-1956, 1 volume (Box 27)
    - 1956-1957, 1 volume (Box 27)
    - 1957-1958, 1 volume (Box 27)
    - 1958-1959, 1 volume (Box 27)
    - 1959-1968, 127 items (Box 28)
      These are not bound. Number of items for each year is as follows: 1959-1960 (17); 1960-1961 (16); 1961-1962 (17); 1961-1962 (14); 1963-1964 (17); 1964-1965 (15); 1966-1967 (15); 1967-1968 (16).
  - School Visitors' reports, 1833-1884, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Town deposit fund (Box 7)
    - Dividends, 1830-1881, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Orders, 1833-1856. undated (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
    - Receipts from, 1841-1855 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer's book, 1837-1868 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1837-1856 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer's book, 1799-1809 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Series 8. Church Records, 1862-1884
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 7)
    - Election of trustees, 1865-1870 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Subscription list, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Series 9. Election Records, 1855-1967
  - Admission of electors, 1862-1884, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Certifications of electors, 1855-1876 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Election notices, 1884-1894 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Election returns
    - Constitutional amendments, 1876-1877 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Federal, State, Local, 1858-1886, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - State officers, 1857-1878 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 1918 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Forfeited rights, 1936-1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Registrars' meeting notices, 1894-1896 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Soldier ballots, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Voter lists
    - Certified and check list, 1868-1873 (Box 16)
    - Certified and check list, 1871-1879 (Box 16)
    - Certified list, 1874-1879 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1876 (Box 16)
    - Certified and check list, 1877 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1878-1879 (Box 16)
    - Certified and check list, 1879-1880 (Box 16)
    - Certified list, 1880-1881 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1880-1882 (Box 16)
    - Certified and check list, 1881-1882 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1882-1884 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1883-1884 (Box 16)
    - Certified list, 1884-1885 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1884-1885 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1885 (Box 16)
    - Certified list, 1886 (Box 16)
    - Certified and check list, 1886-1888 (Box 16)
    - Check list, 1888-1889 (Box 17)
    - Check list, 1888 (Box 17)
    - Check list, 1890 (Box 17)
    - Certified list, 1890-1892 (Box 17)
    - Certified list, 1892-1893 (Box 17)
    - Check list, 1892-1893 (Box 17)
    - Certified list, 1894-1895 (Box 17)
    - Check list, 1894-1895 (Box 17)
    - Check list, 1895 (Box 17)
    - Certified list, 1896 (Box 18)
    - Check list, 1896-1897 (Box 18)
    - Check list, 1897 (Box 18)
    - Certified list, 1898 (Box 18)
    - Check list, 1898-1899 (Box 18)
    - Certified list, 1900 (Box 18)
    - Certified list, 1902 (Box 18)
    - Check list, 1902 (Box 18)
    - Certified list, 1904-1906 (Box 19)
    - Check list, 1904-1906 (Box 19)
    - Certified list, 1906-1908 (Box 19)
    - Check list, 1906-1908 (Box 19)
    - Certified list, 1908-1910 (Box 19)
    - Check list, 1908-1909 (Box 19)
    - Certified list, 1910-1912 (Box 19)
    - Check list, 1910-1912 (Box 19)
    - Check list, 1912-1916 (Box 20)
    - Certified list, 1916-1919 (Box 20)
    - Check list, 1916-1920 (Box 20)
    - Woman's certified list, 1912-1920 (Box 20)
    - Woman's check list, 1912 (Box 20)
    - Woman's check list, 1912 (Box 20)
    - Democratic Party book, 1916-1921 (Box 20)
    - Republican Party book, 1916-1918 (Box 20)
    - Check list, 1932-1934 (Box 20)
    - Record of applicants for admission as voters, 1899-1940; 1 volume + 1 folder (Box 20)
      Includes list of "Ladies made voters Sept 18, 1820".
      Folder contains loose items, 1912-1944, removed from volume such as lists of voters, correspondence, notifications of change of residence of voters.
- Series 10. Tax Records, 1812-1939
  - Abatements, 1817-1933; 1 volume (Box 12)
  - Abatements, 1812-1866, undated (Box 8, Folder 8-12)
  - Assessment books (Box 8)
    - School district No. 2, 1880-1884, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - School district No. 9, 1897, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - District Nos. 13, 7, 10, 1885, 1888, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - List books, 1811, 1815, 1817-1821, 1825-1826, 1828-1837, 1839, 1841-1844, undated; 28 items (Box 15)
    There are three list books for 1820 and two list books for 1843.
  - Individual tax lists, 1878-1928
    - 1878-1894, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - 1916, 1917, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 11 volumes
      Individual tax lists for years 1916 to 1928 are not boxed and do not have item numbers assigned. Researchers should request these items by year.
  - Papers, 1838-1913 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Tax abstracts, 1870-1939
    - 1870, 1874, 1875-1880, 1878-1880, 4 volumes (Box 29)
      The volume covering 1875-1880 is for Ellsworth.
    - 1881, 1884-1885, 1887-1888, 1889, 4 volumes (Box 30)
    - 1892, 1894, 1897, 1899-1902, 4 volumes (Box 31)
    - 1901-1902, 1903-1906, 2 volumes (Box 32)
    - 1907-1909, 1910, 1911, 3 volumes (Box 33)
    - 1912, 1914, 1915-1916, 1917-1918, 1919-1920, 1921-1922, 1923-1924, 1925-1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 21 volumes
      Tax abstracts for 1912 to 1939 are not boxed and do not have item numbers assigned. Researchers should request these items by year.
  - Tax liens, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Series 11. Committee Records, 1939, 1976
  - Bicentennial Committee
    - Minutes, correspondence and ephemera, 1939, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Bicentennial scrapbook, 1939; 1 volume (Box 33)